We cannot lead other people to their breakthrough from our brokenness.
That's, you putting that on a mug?
Because that right there is so profound.
First of all, so many people don't even feel like they need to help others.
They fear their brokenness, not realizing that like there's so much strength.
Yes.
And that's particularly to bring it back to our educators.
The reason that our work and the heart and spirit part of our work is so important
is because if you don't do that, like you can learn all the skills and all that stuff,
but you are inevitably going to have to fight against something.
Something is going to come against you.
And if you haven't actually done the work to deal with the limiting beliefs
and all the other bullshit that we carry, then you won't be able to withstand that.